Okay, okay, so I guess I'll wait for some people to get in here and I talk hopefully
Pleasants, okay?
Originally a streamer has this thing blocking the most of the chat and so it's hard to see
They turn it this way. Maybe that's a little better. I can do some vertical. Okay
Hey, what's going on here? That's a kind of
Library event, okay
Hello, yeah
I have to do it for my computer. Good to see you. Hi, everybody. Hi, brave little toaster. How are you?
That's where I'm going. Favorite restaurant.
Yeah, this will be a peaceful, I'm trying, this will be my, uh, my mea culpa apology. Um,
eating a little bit of crow. Um, you know, please forgive me. Um, the problem is like, you know,
I am, I try not to
Usually try not to think that happens. I hope there's going to be some empathy about it. Like, you know
right
The answer is like I've I've myself
been through a
Lot of a lot of things and you know under accusations and bullying and all that
And so I'm sensitive to that and it's like and so something will happen. I'm also like very stubborn
And I don't like to be told what to do.
And if you know me, you know that's true,
especially like on my show and stuff.
And so when I'm like ordered around, oh, do this, do that,
especially by some people that haven't always had my back
and more or best interest in mind, you know,
I can be resisted out in the app.
Hold on, right back.
Yeah, it's a little dinner thing.
Okay, so anyway, if you're like one of the casualties
in the recent thing with me,
And, you know, maybe it hated me for some certain reason,
then we went back and forth and it's like, you know,
things got ugly.
No, maybe I do owe some people an apology
because when I'm attacked, I tend to fight back.
Okay, now there's no fries here on this deal, the fuck.
Okay.
Well, let me see if I can, I don't have a reward.
Well, let's get a regular thing, what's the value?
Should I get snack wraps?
Then you get something to eat and drink, okay.
the coffee. Anyway, so, you know, I think I owe an apology probably to Kate, but at the same time,
maybe, you know, I don't expect one, but it'd be nice to get an apology from her. I would,
I mean, I know I did that stupid Shrek video or whatever. I deleted it, but she did, you know,
terrible things about me and organized the boycott and everything. There's no reason for the boycott
anymore, unless you really do consider me some kind of abuser of animals, but it's like, if you know
So, okay, hold on a second, kind of a controversial person, I'm not gonna ever say his name again.
I don't have anything to say about him personally. I'll just say, you know, I feel kind of like
I put a lot at stake and then for pretty much to be like, you know, bitten in the ass with it, but
yeah, so I made a mistake and that's what I will say.
And then I got embroiled in a bunch of like, you know, conflicts with other people that,
you know, I really don't have anything against, but when they say things about me, I get the
order right.
Okay.
You got it.
Right.
By them.
Because things were said that maybe, I mean, I can ask, I can forgive them.
I definitely can.
I'm a forgiving person and it wasn't even like personal.
It was like, but it got, it got, it was starting to get personal, right?
It was um, it was not even personal. It's just I felt attacked and I attacked back far from it, right?
Lot of relationships were ruined over it and maybe you know
It was just it just all ended up bad for me, right? So I'm willing I'm willing to that. I'm willing
certain people, right? Okay complete order
I'll go sit down again
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Do I stick this stupid thing?
I think it's beeping at me. Beep, beep, beep.
Insert tap or show I'm tapping it.
Okay, there it goes.
Okay, it was approved.
It's better. More McDonald's than I had in months.
Okay. Okay.
Get to the table.
Yeah, I hope I can make it.
You know, to come back, you know,
basically, you know, I just, like,
it was... then I reacted, and I also...
I will I fight back a little bit because I'm very can be defensive and stuff
But it turns out maybe I was wrong and most people were right and what they were telling me was like
you know, I'm not necessarily a 100% right, but maybe like that wasn't a that wasn't a snake's nest that I wanted to
To get into a vipers den or whatever brave little toaster. Hey, Ilya. How are you? Yeah, meow. Yeah
McDonald's I just got more McDonald's than I have in months. I usually
But five times like, maybe I should get on the one,
McDonald's Wi-Fi, hold on a second.
Okay, so anyway, I'm on the McDonald's Wi-Fi now, I think.
So anyway, you can pass out my,
you can let people know, new haircut now?
I just, I have my hair tied back today.
Now my beard is turning totally gray,
and it's turning totally gray.
So I'm aging in this process, but do I look okay?
I don't know.
Like, uh, sometimes it's like, uh, I don't think I look that much like younger, like on Samans,
they tend to like, like to play this, um, or put this picture up of me, like, you know,
with the haircut, like, I just got out of the shower and then smiling and then like a picture
of me, like, oh, like waking up in the first thing in the morning and like...
Are they eating something or something like that and yeah, it looks like different
But it's that you can also you know show Pamela Anderson without makeup and she looks quite different, right?
I mean, it's like not like I'm Pamela Anderson. I don't know people just don't get that. I make I make a high-butterfly
It's good. I'm okay. I did it but um, but uh, then I went to um, I
Went to like my old friends. So my old friends, you know like summer and you know Alex McQueen and everybody was on um
But money for 20 channel. I got up there. There is no
You know Christine there's no bronze bird. It was just like, you know, just a bunch of people just like
Laughing and joking around having fun. It was like so nice. Yeah
Yeah, I was have a good friend, you know in the community
I was able to talk to you and like express a lot of feelings to and let know what was going on and
You know, I just feel like I have really great friends
And that's like really why, you know, I came to YouTube like or whatever and do this for like basically that I make friends and to have fun
it wasn't about like, oh
doxing and love and
Accusations and you know blah blah blah and I it's like I regret I got into the situation and it's like so I have apologies and it's like
Um, you know, and it was like, it's like, and I was gone on way too long, maybe two months
It's gone on or something like that.
Any new day experiences?
Hmm.
Well, J-Dog, I need to get a contact with J-Dog, because J-Dog offered to like take me, pick
me up this weekend or something like that, but I'm ready to take his email address down.
So J-Dog, if you're watching, you know, I'll have to give you my information or something
like that backstage next time, because I'm like, I'm not really good at.
Doing that stuff. So J-Dog if you want to still anyway, and then maybe like I guess 300 glow is saying that he wants to
Go out with him and his wife to who knows what will happen. I mean, it's like it's gonna be a BS
It's gonna be a fiesta either way, right?
No matter who I go I go out with them. Just kidding. Yeah, I do I do I do enjoy Hispanic. It's Hispanic people
But in a respect and in a respectful way, I know these are all straight guys and
But who knows so anyway, yeah, it's gonna be nice night to chill. I just got my mcdonald
I don't like how it keeps cutting out and my wife is not on someone's someone's some know-it-all was trying to tell me
You know, I'm gonna say
Let me just make sure my mcdonald's Wi-Fi is on
Anyway, it's going painfully slow have I been talking to Tommy James no and that's one person that I won't be apologizing to
That's one person that that did go too far. I mean he went kind of far last night with what he was saying
Um, I don't know his situation with his cats.
I really don't, and it's like I miss that kind of,
and so if I pre-judged him, and I might have said things
that I didn't mean, and he kind of, like,
you know, porn bombed me a couple times,
but I still, you know, at the end of the day,
I like the guy.
But, um, Tommy James, no, I can't stand.
I cannot stand him.
Nope, I will not be apologizing to him.
Wow, look at these fries.
He fungus.
Okay.
I know it's getting really annoying. I don't know why it keeps going in and out. I do have my Wi-Fi off
So I don't know what it's doing that. I couldn't turn the McDonald's went on it
But it's like my one's going a little slow, but I'm okay. So thank you
I can't even eat it because it's so hot right now, but even the coffee is too hot home
History, yeah, IRL history, but me apologize
I know I've done a couple of apology streams like a one time I had to apologize to Alex McQueen
Because he sent me McDonald's I went to the wrong house. So I thought he like was lying
And then he turned out it's extended because I saw it the next morning next to next door neighbor's house and I got it
Yeah, IRL history. Well, history was made last night. Most people missed it
Like I there was somebody I got to like share the stream or stream with but I don't know if I'll clip that or anything
But it was not a it did not go well
It did not go well and it's not going well, but it's like I think that it's like I'm just I'm just saying to that person
they know who they are, it's like, you know,
nothing against you, like, particularly,
but it's like, I feel like I put myself out there a lot,
and I'm on the line for this person,
and I feel kind of disrespected, but it's okay.
And it's like, that person wants to go ahead
and start to keep, like, now get really nasty
and attacking me, that's not a very good idea.
And I would say I'm gonna leave his name out of my mouth,
and he can leave my name, everybody's name out of my mouth.
So, yeah, it is IRL history.
There are 28 people in here.
I don't know. It says no internet connection.
Do you see me?
Oh, there's Arthur.
So, I owe Arthur an apology, I guess.
Arthur, I'll still let you.
I'll still let you on the show.
If you'll take my apology.
I don't expect an apology from you.
You said nasty things, and it wasn't really involving you,
but I'm sorry, Arthur.
Okay?
I hope you can be friends with me.
He can.
I mean, the person has their own platform.
I don't know why.
It's like they kind of felt the need to like,
you know, kind of monopolize it,
Then this treat me about it, but not you but Arthur is thinking where you can be back in the psych kitty gate
Okay, thank you Arthur. I mean, I'm sorry. I mean, I
Apologies a few people but a couple people went too far. I don't think I'll be an apology, but but
You're the most part, you know, I love I love most of you guys and you know, I made a mistake
And I understand if some people won't forgive me and some people still hate me or some people go after me or whatever
I can't really prevent that but
I just as much as I can, I'm sorry.
So let's go for a walk.
You desire all the, yeah, exactly.
It's like, and that's what I kind of missing.
Like last night when I went to,
I was able to go to Money 420s
and then like, you know, it was summer
and like, I guess Harry was there and Alex McQueen.
I think and a ghost and stuff and we're all just bullshitting and laughing and I was doing terror readings and
It was just so fun. And I was like, what happened to this? I said, I haven't done this. Where have I been?
I've been like in like some kind of like like delusional
You know, like nightmarish
Like like state of mind and land and it's like I think we're what happened to this. It was so much fun
That's how it should always be. It's like that's how it was. Maybe like last
Wars and their meme wars and everything and I'm making horrible music videos. It's like I mean
I'm going to get into a better vibration about it and uh, I'm more fun
I guess like I guess it's probably not fun for the audience either
Well, I know there's there's some drama people here and I know there's a lot of trolls
um
But I don't I mean it's like I like some of the trolls. I didn't like when
But then it got like you could tell her to get not funny. I got her to get too serious
And it was like, it's not about that.
I'm not like, Geraldo.
I prefer more like to be like Jerry Springer
or like Howard Stern, you know?
Not like Geraldo where it's like,
I'm getting involved in the middle of like
the audience disbites and getting like, you know,
strapped and, and getting hit with a, you know,
some KKK member, you know, hitting me upside the head
with the plywood board or something like that.
I don't want that.
I want to be standing with security, like, you know,
in front of me.
take away all the crazies, right?
Which I will do next time.
I mean, I understand there's a serious mental health issues
involved with some of these people,
like especially the person that I was dealing with.
And so, you know, I have empathy and sympathy for that.
But at the same time, it's like,
I can't take on just months and months.
And it's like, this person, that person,
I don't know most of these people.
Nor do I care to get involved.
Okay, here I'm at the store.
Oh my gosh.
I don't know how many to carry all this stuff.
Okay, this copy is pretty good hot.
The food's all hot.
I'm sorry, hi.
Okay, hold on a second.
So I'm at the place where everyone said
that was stealing from me.
No, I was not stealing from here.
She'll confirm it.
If you want me to hurt you, go here.
But if I did, they would not let me shop here probably.
How are you doing?
Okay, can I get three Swisher, please?
Can I bag?
Give like a bigger bag like I need like a big bag like one of those. Yeah, I get that back. Yeah
I can carry myself
Good. Yeah, it's good
No, it's a pin or something, but it says thank you, but then I said what it said. Oh
Thank you, I'll answer it the next time. Okay. Thank you
Machines are a little bit. Okay. Here we go. Okay. We get to go home
Okay, I'm carrying everything.
The weather will be yours.
We're looking rough as hell.
Oh, shut the fuck up, rogue nomad.
It's because I'm in the fucking sun.
You look rough as hell.
Oh, you're using some shit.
I look fucking good for my age.
I'm 45 years old, you know?
I'm not puppy.
I'm like, you know, I look fucking good.
I do have gray in my beard, maybe.
And it's like, you know,
don't have to say anything about my appearance
when you're not even showing your appearance.
I'm so sick of people that do that.
When you are on camera and stuff and I see exactly what you look like and then I can see you get up
And you know what you look like first thing in the morning
This is my morning
Then you can like, you know, you can tease me about my looks when you're you sitting there with your muscular glamour shot
Avatar because it's your muscles
Try until like you know fool me
You know
I'm so lame
You say, oh, you say oh you're having a rough time and you look like a little stressed or something like that your little
little bitch friend Vita who's come screaming at me right ex fiancee or
whoever that she has posted everywhere on Instagram and Tik Tok or whatever and
other people have already docs but I'm I got struck for her right everybody else
she had no problem with anybody else that did it but she still brings that oh
you posted my and she has to come and attack my mods and Katie and who Katie
who she had on the month so be it I've already apologized for that shit you
know and you're just saying never accept the apology so like that's your it's on
You owe me an apology for putting me through all this shit and talking about me.
Just assuming he said it's my fault.
You see their hammer or it's like some of the dirt.
But I know he likes to cage me.
Looks like I have in his bag today.
Let's see, the coffee is like fucking hot as hell.
Stop calling when I'm on the phone.
Okay, I'm back.
Jesus.
Hold on, now I have to do my stuff down for a second.
Hold on.
Stop calling me!
Okay.
Okay, well you can take a time out.
You did what are your thoughts about being um timed out in the chat? It's like uh
I'm about to dox the phone number next time you call me like
I'm reading the phone number out loud and then people can start calling you how about that
I don't mind doxing a phone number. That's harassing me. It's not doxing
anyway
Yeah, so not an edge over anything. I'm like actually like I'm very clear
Alexandra and I are absolutely fine and like that relationship has nothing to do with the other
See, okay, I'm busy for a while go ruin that text down number or whatever
I'm doxxing and some text now and we're probably
Texas
Yeah, again, if I have to get nasty with people I will but
I'm trying to apologize and uh
They want to like fucking go back and forth. I mean, I would I didn't say anything negative about that person
I was like I didn't
I don't have to go wherever I want, you know, to that person.
Do you think that I'm not allowed to go around?
I was born a biological female. I, you know, I went through a gender transition,
at the same time I had my nose job. I was very embarrassed that that's what's getting public
because I was trying to keep that secret. I like, I like to look on a guy's face when he
goes down on me and he sees a vagina instead of a penis. And so, yes, I was born a woman.
Sir, okay, don't call me ma'am. Don't call me ma'am
Call me sir. Don't call me ma'am. I'm the opposite of the of the other kind of trans transgender person, right?
You know and so I think I qualify as a man now, okay?
And I had my my breasts removed and my my vagina enlarged
So leave me the fuck alone
You transphobic son of a bitch
Okay
I'm home.
Docs me from the clear, blue sky, motherfucker.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Hold on.
I'll leave it on till I get inside.
See what happens.
Okay.
Can't wait to go see the comments and stuff.
They're just kind of fun.
I don't really care about any of this.
So, yeah, okay.
Anyway, I'm home.
Okay.
Here I am, the one that you love.
Yeah, okay.
We're gonna get the Adam's apple.
I got, oh, I had an artificial Adam's apple
inserted into my throat.
So to make me look more masculine.
Yeah.
Well, that's what, that's the rumor going around now
is that I was born a biological female.
So, oh yeah.
You know, now it's being said, you know,
my name is, I won't say the name,
but they say that I was born a biological female.
So that's true.
I'm just admitting it to everybody now.
But anyway, here's who I owe an apology to.
Probably careless Kate.
Maybe, maybe, clumsy being gay, maybe.
I need an apology from him though, too.
Never tell me James.
I need an apology from Bita.
I don't, I owe an apology to Kate.
I owe an apology to a lot of the audience.
I owe an apology, no, it's not actually true.
It is not true.
But I wish it was because that'd be cool
That'd be kind of like a unique thing about me and then I could like you know call you know stay transphobia if I ever get bullied and stuff
But no, it's uh, fortunately, it's not true. I wish I was born a female. I mean, it's like I love women
I mean that'd be cool, but I was born a woman. I wouldn't like you know
Pick this is my masculine. I was like probably stay a woman and date a bunch of guys, but
Yeah, because the only live one so
Yeah, someone's saying I'm just being I'm being a little silly. I know this part of my like silly sense of humor
Okay, hold on
But it's an interesting theory. I mean it's like people believe that to them, you know
But if you see me in like my speedo, you know, it's not true
And everyone's seeing my speedo pretty much
You never heard that one. Yeah, I know that was my see without seeds
That was my April Fool's joke was I wanted to become like turned into a woman and stuff like that
Um, men can have periods as well.
Well, men are always on their period.
Women just, like, you know, are lucky enough just to have once a month with a little bit more blood.
But men are always kind of, like, aggravated, right?
I'm just kidding. Okay, sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't want to be offensive to anybody.
I don't want to be offensive. Okay, cool.
Well, men can be bitches, too. Yeah.
Especially some gay guys, but I'm not like the, I'm not like, I'm not like a bitchy gay guy.
I'm not, I'm really not.
Well, I have been a little bit recently.
So maybe but I try not to be so bitchy, right? Maybe I maybe I'll off my period finally
You ever see head wig in the angry inch? It's a really funny movie about this like this this like gay Eastern European
Like I think he's from like, you know, East West Germany or something and he marries like an American like a black American
Military person, but in order to get to America. He has to have a sex change. Okay. You have to poop. Okay. Go ahead Canada cry
Are you the, you're not the real Canada dry, are you?
Is that something that he would say?
It was bad, oh yeah, you're really, I'm sorry.
It was, I'm sorry.
Yeah, and I know, and then it's like,
that person wasn't very sensitive to that.
And so, I don't like to talk about like all this guy,
but oh, I'm sorry, yeah.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
I think it's Canada, Canada cry.
Is Christine in here?
I don't know, I haven't walked probably.
Is she acting tough?
Yeah, Christine I she owes me an apology because I already apologized to Christine and then she's gonna gone after me attacking me again
All I said about Christine was a joke about her being a witch and something about being in the woods sacrificing something
But yeah, I know I know I know
Okay, Canada cry. Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't know if you're the real Canada cry, but
Yeah
Yeah, I know I know I know I know it's like and it's like and then like you know some people lack sensitivity and it's like
So I'm gonna really like I have any cock rings. No, but when the last one of the last guys I
You know hooked up with whatever had went on it was gross
It was like it was like clear rubber ring and I was like, you know, what's that?
And it's like and then it's like the wiener kind of like was like not even like just hard because of that
I don't know it's weird and then and then he left it on my sink and I threw it in the trash
Yeah, Rob no spamming
We're back to square one, Rob. She's recapping me. Oh, that's good. Well, is she mad? I mean, it's like
Oh, she's live with INX. Okay. Well, I hope they're not mad
I mean, it's like all that happened was I mean, I have nothing against INX. I had a good time with her
I still would be willing to have her on the show
But the person that I was like spending and you know having platforming allowing to say anything
He wanted and stuff like that. I had nothing bad to say about INX
But I did go to Crystal Anne's and I just wanted to talk to her
And Gamble and Kew were there, I got super early attacked, I was told to shut up and
that I was going to be killed and Kew was going to come over and slice my throat and,
you know, bash my head in and all this kind of stuff. And so it wasn't like exactly like me,
You know whatever but yeah, and it's like you know what and anybody's welcome to be friends with whoever they want
I'm not saying oh choose them or me or anything like that
I'm like I'm happy to have people have friends and people have and we can have mutual friends and not necessarily like the person
But yeah, I appreciate I appreciate Alexandra and even if like, you know
She you know for some for something, you know, she would decide that she didn't like you know want to be
associated with me anymore. I just wanted to, you know, I'll say, you know, I love her and
thank you for everything. And, you know, thank you for being there and stuff. And it's like,
but I have nothing against her. I don't think that there's a problem. But, you know, it's like,
they are going to try to, you know, say, oh, you know, make, you know, give ultimatums, not them.
I'm not her, but I'm saying them, you know, or, you know, not that one person, because I have
She might have like old phone calls and conversations and it's like, you know, that's what happens is like sometimes, you know
People go through different phases with people, right?
And it's like and so, you know, but I think Alexander understands like we were fighting at a period of time and stuff like that and you know anyway
So she you know keeps me will get it
They're talking shit. It's okay
What's going on? Okay. I know it's fine that she's live with them, but it's like, you know, so but
You know, I actually, like, I encouraged Brandon to become for the INX, right?
And I have to, I mean, I'm sorry, I'm not trying to talk about him.
I said I'm not going to talk about him, so I'm not going to talk to him.
Basically, I'm trying to talk to everybody else.
I'm leaving him out of my mouth, okay?
But I was I just was getting like, you know
Call bombed and stuff like that. So I have all these problems with these different people
And so it's a lot to it's a lot to juggle at once
I'm trying to just apologize to most people and I've been saying I don't have anything against that person
But but if they want to get if he wants to get the derby and stuff like that, you know, I mean
You know, then I do have the right to like respond, right? So anyway, I
don't
Well in BlackRG, you're one of the people that I do agree with him about and yeah
Go ahead and look at that website called
What's it called?
Well, let's give you the initials. It's called KF and you're all over that website
Go read that and you'll see your picture with your dog. I didn't put it there
They're already way, you know, you have a big history of them talking about you and yeah, so go ahead and
You can just go away
You're one of the people that I do not own apology to
But I'm not gonna reach I won't I'll be restreaming her unless you know
She she was to give me permission for that because I I need to like make sure everything's cool right now
Yeah, I mean it's like and I knew that um, you know
They're allowed to give their opinion and stuff like that, but if they're gonna go over there
Let's see. Yeah, do you?
Whoo
But I just hope that I mean, it's like I hope that people just don't start taking sides and stuff like that
But I yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, there's really an aside looks like I'm about to be thrown under my bus
You're getting a karma
What 53 brandon and and INX, right?
Well ship and sip you're another person that you know, you were very disloyal and you know, you can take a time out
You're about to get your karma bad. You're about to get your karma bad
Hey, hey, you need to fix your stupid channel and on um on a rumble
Okay, how about you got your karma because that you miss the best beat episodes, you know in the world?
Yeah, so some people you know, I'm just be happy to be hiding and stuff like that
No, I know that you know, Alexandra. I hope is well, you know, we maintain a neutrality about the situation
but you know, she's like I know that she
Of course, we'll let him speak and stuff like that.
So that's good.
I mean, he can have anybody that wants to platform him can.
And I don't have a problem with her doing that.
So I would hope that it doesn't turn into some kind of like,
I'm sure that they're bashing, right?
You're lightly armed with an airsoft.
OK, well, Butterfly.
I don't know if you're serious or not Butterfly.
That sounds kind of crazy.
Yeah, so you can see the moon is out tonight. It's beautiful beautiful night. It's a gorgeous night. Actually
I've got all these TV sets behind me. They're glowing. I do have a new video here. Let's watch my new video and
Everybody's talkin', everybody's sellin' dreams
But the truth leaks out between the broken seams
The Oracle Buffering
Loading, lo-lo-lo-lo-loading